<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BALAMURUGAN PERIYASAMY</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BALAMURUGAN PERIYASAMY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Latte - 03 MAY 2020</title>
      <link>/news-letter/sunday-latte-03-may-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-letter/sunday-latte-03-may-2020/</guid>
      <description>Guess maximum possible loss and profit made in Nifty this year? Answers at the bottom.
Here are the intereting things I came across the web last week:
Why are stock markets when world is going down? Link  Markets are smart in punishing the impacted companies(Exxon) and rewarding others(Amazon) Market is optimistic which doesnt tie well with reality yet  Can you trust Covid19 models? Link  Models are tough especially when input is dynamic A small change of R_0, viral spread rate, from 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Latte - 26 April 2020</title>
      <link>/news-letter/weekly-reading-25-april-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-letter/weekly-reading-25-april-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here are few good articles from last week readings
Career advice for people with bad luck  Politics emerge when the players believe the game is zero sum. Try not to learn the wrong habits. Failure I call living  Give a full read, worth it
How to overcome mental laziness  If you have already reached reading till this, you don&#39;t need them :) Few gems from the conversation:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description> Coming Soon
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description>Hey ! Welcome to the Balamurugan&#39;s Blog
Take a look around my journals on datascience,learnings and about me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/license/</guid>
      <description>You can use this page to put a license on the contents of your blog, like so:
 The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright (c) 2020 Balamurugan Periyasamy
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>