<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BALAMURUGAN PERIYASAMY</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BALAMURUGAN PERIYASAMY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to test stastical significance?</title>
      <link>/post/statsignificance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/statsignificance/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel</title>
      <link>/blog/excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:45:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/excel/</guid>
      <description>Excel is indispensable for two reasons: Easy for business users Goto tool for many years so tough to move away Best User friendly CURD (Create, Udpate, Read and Delete) tool ever built(in my opinion)
However excel seriously lacks below: A C I Frequent crash and ability to start from where it was left(Durability)
Interesting links on excel:
http://veekaybee.github.io/2018/09/08/excel/ http://www.eusprig.org/horror-stories.htm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Career Capital</title>
      <link>/blog/data-science-career-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 23:02:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/data-science-career-capital/</guid>
      <description>I am a big believer in Cal Newport/Steve Martin&amp;rsquo;s philosophy of one should get too good to be ignored. How can one get build their skill set? Cal Newport answer is building a deep work habit for x hours. This is a lead measure to achieve your future goal of to be a better data scientist.
Who is a best data scientist? One who creates a product that directly contributes to increasing revenue or cutting cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to do too good to be ignored Data Science</title>
      <link>/blog/how-to-do-too-good-to-be-ignored-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 21:59:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-to-do-too-good-to-be-ignored-data-science/</guid>
      <description>Data science is the art of converting business problem to data problem to data solution to business solution as a quote goes.
Doing sophisticated Data science work sincerely and removing the expectations of result will not help. Data science should aim for atleast one of the below: 1) Increase revenue 2) Reduce cost 3) Better forecast 4) Remove complexity 5) Help someone to do these effectively with analysis
Above all one should garner the respect of the stakeholders</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 10 27 Hello World</title>
      <link>/blog/2018-10-27-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 11:39:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018-10-27-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>##Hello World</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>With this theme, it is possible to add small sections that only contains one page like this. It will automatically appears in the header, at the end.
Along with Ford Prefect, Dent barely escapes the Earth&amp;rsquo;s destruction as it is demolished to make way for a hyperspace bypass. Arthur spends the next several years, still wearing his dressing gown, helplessly launched from crisis to crisis while trying to straighten out his lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 20:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>In this theme, it is possible to add sections like a Projects one for example. You can add plenty of articles about your projects and a presentation page that will be displayed before the list. All is modulable, if you don&amp;rsquo;t want something.
A Hollywood-funded film version, produced and filmed in the UK, was released in April 2005, and radio adaptations of the third, fourth, and fifth novels were broadcast from 2004 to 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description>This is the home page. It will display the blog section if there is one, and a text before.
Hey ! Welcome to the Cocoa Enhanced theme. Here are some articles :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/license/</guid>
      <description>You can use this page to put a license on the contents of your blog, like so:
 The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2015 Nishanth Shanmughamnishanth.gerrard@gmail.com
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>