<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News Letter on BALAMURUGAN PERIYASAMY</title>
    <link>/news-letter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News Letter on BALAMURUGAN PERIYASAMY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/news-letter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Latte - 07-Jun-20</title>
      <link>/news-letter/sunday-latte-07-jun-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-letter/sunday-latte-07-jun-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here are the few interesting things I came across the web this week.
Which category of mutual funds even the worst performer in the last one year return is 9% investing in relatively safe assets? Answer in the last section.
Effects Link Hawthorne effect: Modifying action if someone is observing
John Henry effect: In an experiment, if group A is compared with other preferentially treated group B, members of group A actively work harder to overcome the &amp;ldquo;disadvantage&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Latte - 31 MAY 2020</title>
      <link>/news-letter/sunday-latte-31-may-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-letter/sunday-latte-31-may-2020/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Next Wednesday’s meeting has been moved forward two days. What day is Wednesday’s meeting now?”Answer at the bottom
Hugging saint Link Amma aka Hugging saint from Kerala is famous for her hugs and whisper in ears. Now there is a ban on hugging and darshan in her ashram due to covid. Who said pivoting is only for startups?
American Factory - Documentary I watched recently Link  This documentary produced by Obamas won Oscars last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Latte - 17 MAY 2020</title>
      <link>/news-letter/sunday-latte-17-may-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-letter/sunday-latte-17-may-2020/</guid>
      <description>Guess Zoom is bigger than how many world&#39;s biggest airlines combined. Answer at the bottom.
Procrastination Link  Why? &amp;ldquo;Task is boring,difficult or we’re worried about failing&amp;rdquo; Effects? &amp;ldquo;Host of adverse mental and physical health consequences, including anxiety and depression, poor health such as colds and flu, and even more serious conditions like cardiovascular disease.&amp;quot; How to overcame? The article recommends as said in frozen 2, &amp;ldquo;Do the next tiny right thing&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Latte - 10 MAY 2020</title>
      <link>/news-letter/sunday-latte-10-may-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-letter/sunday-latte-10-may-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here are the intereting things I came across the web last week:
Bitcoing is halving.So what? Link  Bitcoin block reward will decrease from 12.5 to 6.25 coins from tomorrow When last two times this happened, Bitcoin increased 8,500% in 2013 and almot 3,000% in 2016. Yes, percentages are double checked and this rise was over 12-18 months period after halving. Bitocoin crashed around 40%($7.9k to 4.9k) in a March and recovered 100%($9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Latte - 03 MAY 2020</title>
      <link>/news-letter/sunday-latte-03-may-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-letter/sunday-latte-03-may-2020/</guid>
      <description>Guess maximum possible loss and profit made in Nifty this year? Answers at the bottom.
Here are the intereting things I came across the web last week:
Why are stock markets when world is going down? Link  Markets are smart in punishing the impacted companies(Exxon) and rewarding others(Amazon) Market is optimistic which doesnt tie well with reality yet  Can you trust Covid19 models? Link  Models are tough especially when input is dynamic A small change of R_0, viral spread rate, from 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Latte - 26 April 2020</title>
      <link>/news-letter/weekly-reading-25-april-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-letter/weekly-reading-25-april-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here are few good articles from last week readings
Career advice for people with bad luck  Politics emerge when the players believe the game is zero sum. Try not to learn the wrong habits. Failure I call living  Give a full read, worth it
How to overcome mental laziness  If you have already reached reading till this, you don&#39;t need them :) Few gems from the conversation:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>